

Oksana Kravchenko

Phone number: +48791350961

Email: kravchenko.oksanna@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/oksana-kravchenko-a10461252/

Portfolio: https://github.com/KravchenkoOksanna/Portfolio.git

Age: 26

City: Krakow/Ready to relocate

Employment options: office/remote

Summary

Trainee QA engineer. I have a good understanding of QC processes, requirements, methodology, and tools. Good knowledge and understanding of different types of tests (regression, functional, load, etc). Experience in writing/creating test documentation (test cases, checklists, test plans, bug reports). Experience with bug tracking systems, test management tools, API testing tools, Database. I have High communication, organization skills, and quick learning skills; positive, responsible, and flexible person.

Technical skills

Operation Systems

- Microsoft Windows
- MacOS

Tools and Technologies

- Technical Documentation / SRS
- Jira, Trello, Mantis, Confuence
- TestRail, TestLink
- HTML/CSS
- MySQL
- Xpath
- XML
- JSON
- Selenium IDE
- Fiddler Everywhere
- Postman
- JMeter
- Git, GitHub
- SourceTree
- KDiff3

Other

- Agile
- SCRUM
- Waterfall
- Kanban

Experience

Sales Manager | CSP TETŁAK & RADŁOWSKI SPÓŁKA KOMANDYTOWA

Cracow - July 2019 - Current

Responsibilities:

- selling supplies and services via phone calls;
- monitoring and reporting on own sales performance analytics weekly, monthly, and quarterly;
- responsibility for the control of the whole sales life cycle;
- achievement sales targets;
- evaluated performance against goals and implemented appropriate development plans.

Customer Support Representative CCO Contact Center Outsourcing

Cracow - November 2017 - September 2019

Responsibilities:

- assistance and advice to clients through three channels of communication: phone, e-mail, live chat;
- supporting customer questions and issues, evaluating possible resolutions, and implementing best solutions;
- receiving reports of machine, program, and application faults;
- receiving complaints.

Languages

- Ukrainian proficient
- Russian proficient
- Polish advanced
- English intermediate

Certifications

o Nov 2022– May 2023

Quality Assurance practice (ua)

Nataliia Popelyshko

o Oct 2022

GoIT English HTML (en)

GoIT - start your career in IT

o Oct 2022

Software testing: preparation for certification ISTQB Foundation (ru) Stepik

o Sep 2022

Fundamentals of the Software Testing (en)

QATestLab

o Sep 2022

Fundamentals of software testing (ua)

Prometheus

o Sep 2022

${\bf Software\ testing\ for\ beginners\ } (\it ru)$

Stepik

Jun 2019

Google Analytics, SEO, Content Marketing & Webwriting (pl)

Education

Bachelor of Science - Oct 2014 - Apr 2018 PWSZ Name of Szymona Szymonowica | Poland Political Science Oct 2014 - Apr 2018

Specialization: Policy of security and crisis response

I hereby authorise Acturis Poland Sp. z o.o. to process my personal data included in my job application for the needs of the recruitment process (in accordance with the Act of 29 August 1997 on the Protection of Personal Data (unified text: Journal of Laws of 2002 No. 101 item 926 with amendments). I hereby authorise Acturis Poland sp. z o.o. to process my personal data for the purposes of any future recruitment processes.